<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>India on Jovial Dragon blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/india/</link>
    <description>Recent content in India on Jovial Dragon blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleepless in Singapore</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/sleepless-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/sleepless-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>The last Saturday of my trip was a fairly slow day. I got to bed at 5 in the morning. Ricky said we&amp;rsquo;d all meet for breakfast at 9 so I got up still feeling tired. Ricky didn&amp;rsquo;t get up until about 12. Figures.
Throughout the day we had a stream of people leaving and lots of goodbyes. I went out for a bit of shopping with Tara and Sophia, just so that I could say I did something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIP in Delhi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/vip-in-delhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/vip-in-delhi/</guid>
      <description>After dinner some of Liana&amp;rsquo;s Indian friends arrived in Mercedes cars to pick us up. We drove to the beat club in Delhi. Entry was 2000 rupees, but Mack knew the owner so we got in for free.
  An elephant outside the club   The club was lush. There was a large indoors section, and then a really nice garden area. Mack bought us champagne and vodka. The drinks cost about the same as drinks in Wellington, which by Indian standards is exorbitant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Buddha</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/big-buddha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/big-buddha/</guid>
      <description>Today we went to the place where Buddha gave his first lectures.
We had a fairly long tuktuk ride and then we met a local guide at the Chinese Buddhism shrine.
From there he showed us around the main shrine where we saw the Buddha tree and the golden Buddha. We then went next door to the stump I think it was called. This is a giant concrete mound which was created to commemorate the location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sailing the Ganges</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/sailing-the-ganges/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/sailing-the-ganges/</guid>
      <description>The day before yesterday we caught a sleeper train. It was 13 hours from Agra to Varanasi. We had to get locks and chains for our bags on this one because apparently baggage thefts happen. Apparently the theives throw your luggage off the train for their accomplices to pick up. The ride itself was fairly uneventful. I slept listening to music.
Our new hotel in Varanasi is nice. It seems to be the only nice thing in the city though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agra</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/agra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/agra/</guid>
      <description>It was another early start. I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting used to those as of late. This time it was a train to Agra. The train which we caught was actually a nice one. We had reclining seats, and breakfast was included in our tickets. Ricky ordered some toast and an odd vegetarian sausage for our breakfasts. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t too bad.
  Indian train food   We arrived at Agra and made our way to the hotel via auto-rickshaw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian astronomers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/indian-astronomers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/indian-astronomers/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we took the bus from Pushkar to Jaipur. We had the option of taking a public bus for 6 hours, or paying an extra 150 rupee for a quicker private bus. We opted for the private one.
The girls bought booze for the bus and so got pretty rowdy over the journey. At one point on the bus we saw a mini sand tornado form on the side of the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pushkar monkey crisis</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/the-pushkar-monkey-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/the-pushkar-monkey-crisis/</guid>
      <description>We got up again at 5am to climb a local hill and watch the sunrise. It was pretty tall and there were lots of steps.
Up the top there was a bunch of hippies smoking weed and dancing to electronic music.
There was a temple up the top, but we didn&amp;rsquo;t bother going inside. Behind the temple there were lots of rocks which we climbed to watch the sunrise.
  The sunrise next to the temple   Ricky called over a troop of monkeys and then it was all on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizzas in Pushkar</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/pizzas-in-pushkar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/pizzas-in-pushkar/</guid>
      <description>The day after the party we got up at 10 am. Still too early! We made it to a bakery for breakfast. I had a pizza and it tasted really good.
Afterwards we went on a boat ride on the lake. We circled the lake palace, and saw the place which the Taj Mahal was modeled after. Apparently you can hire out the island for weddings. It costs around $150k. Angelina Jolie an Brad Pitt got married there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party in Udaipur</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/party-in-udaipur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/party-in-udaipur/</guid>
      <description>The bus drive was really long. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough music on my phone, so I kept listening to the same albums on repeat. We had a break at an Indian bus stop. It felt like our tour bought half the store. I got some full toss snacks which were pretty good.
  The indian bus stop     My snacks   After we arrived at our hotel we went on an orientation walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopping safari</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/shopping-safari/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 15:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/shopping-safari/</guid>
      <description>At 5am we caught the public bus to Jodhpur. The bus ride was alright, except for the horn on the bus. They used it frequently, and there were about half a dozen different sounds, each more ridiculous than the last. There didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be a pattern determining their usage. Nobody got much sleep.
  The tower in Jodhpur   We arrived at the polo heritage hotel. This place is really nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Jaisalmer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/lost-in-jaisalmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/lost-in-jaisalmer/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we arrived in Jaisalmer. It&amp;rsquo;s hot here. Luckily the hotel has a pool we can dip our feet in.
We went on an initial orientation walk, and then visited the lake. The girls went on a boat ride while we stayed on the shore. It was really peaceful. I met a guy called Saword who was an airforce engineer. He was really interested about NZ. His wife was there too, hurrying him up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ricky and the rats</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/ricky-and-the-rats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 10:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/ricky-and-the-rats/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we went to visit the fort at Bikaner. It&amp;rsquo;d been built up over many years by many different Raj so there was a huge amount of variation in the architecture.
We saw the royal bedroom. The bed was deliberately low to the ground so that enemies couldn&amp;rsquo;t hide under it.
Many of the rooms were fantastically painted. The old raj really liked their art. Most of the ceilings were pretty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ships of the desert</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/the-ships-of-the-desert/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/the-ships-of-the-desert/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we left the hotel in these small mini vans. I was seated at the back. No seatbelts, no windows. Ricky put on some pumping Bollywood music so we were singing and dancing on our ride through the streets. The Indian roads are interesting. There are two road rules: 1. Drive on the left. 2. Give way to cows. The first isn&amp;rsquo;t strictly adhered to. We arrived at a smallish village where we met our camels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training for Bikaner</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/training-for-bikaner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 04:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/training-for-bikaner/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday evening we went out to another restaurant recommended by Ricky, our guide. It turned out to be a bit of a case of déjà Vu. The menu was identical to that which we went to the night previously. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that the two places are just for tourists. You&amp;rsquo;d never expect to see butter chicken on the menu of a real indian restaurant. I ended up ordering a biryani with a long name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Delhi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/a-day-in-delhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/a-day-in-delhi/</guid>
      <description>Today we got up bright and early for a day trip around Delhi.
We took the metro which was very busy. It&amp;rsquo;s was kinda funny how the front carriage was always reserved for women.
We travelled around some of the oldest streets in Delhi to get to the largest mosque in Asia. Jama Masjid was the name. It was pretty impressive.
  Jama Masjid mosque   Then we went to a Shik temple where they had a book which they fed, sang to, and put to bed at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Gracias</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/no-gracias/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/no-gracias/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve now met the rest of my group. There&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a mix. Lots of people from the UK. We decided to go on a bit of an adventure outside. Lots of dust. So much dust. My eyes were watering. Also lots of stall, all mostly selling the same stuff. Finally there were lots of beggars and sales people. If you say &amp;ldquo;No thank you&amp;rdquo; they keep pestering you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrived</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/arrived/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/arrived/</guid>
      <description>So, I made it to the joining hotel. Somehow. You know how I&amp;rsquo;ve had plenty of warnings never to drink the water in India? What was this first thing I did when I arrived? I made beeline for the nearest drinking fountain and took a sip. Whoops. Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll be ok. After half an hour with some immigration officials who resembled the two Ronnies I managed to get my entry visa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight #2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/flight-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 16:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/flight-2/</guid>
      <description>Forgot to mention in the previous post that Air New Zealand ID&amp;rsquo;d me for alcohol on the flight. Must be my baby face. It&amp;rsquo;s a real pain digging around for you passport while your tray table is full. Before boarding the flight I was paged by the ground crew and quizzed over my visa. I thought I was late for the flight and ended up chucking out my yummy pasta salad which made up dinner #2 :-/ The good: - Metal cutlery - After hours of dry recycled air, orange juice tastes like golden nectar of the gods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight #1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/flight-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 06:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/flight-1/</guid>
      <description>Some pretty cool views of the Makara wind turbines on my way over. It was a pretty good flight. The food was decent. I ended up watching the movie Gravity because I felt like watching a disaster movie about flying above the earth while I was flying above the earth. Best part was the landing. There was a gull with its wings up saying &amp;ldquo;come at me bro&amp;rdquo; to the plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The real departure lounge</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/the-real-departure-lounge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 00:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/the-real-departure-lounge/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently hanging out at the &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; departure lounge (Burger King) waiting for my flight. Too bad I left all of my change at home. Otherwise I&amp;rsquo;d be able to play Metallica pinball while I wait. It&amp;rsquo;s a beautiful Wellington day to be flying out on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To talk of many things</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/india/to-talk-of-many-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 07:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/india/to-talk-of-many-things/</guid>
      <description>Blogs. They&amp;rsquo;re the in thing these days. Nuff said. With any luck this blog will be a vehicle to chronicle my adventures and whatever happens in between. Or I&amp;rsquo;ll get lazy and the last thing you&amp;rsquo;ll know is I am lost in a jungle. Never to be heard from again. Lately I&amp;rsquo;m been doing much planning for my upcoming trip to India. Booking travel insurance isn&amp;rsquo;t very fun. I do however have a list of much less fun things:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>