<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Japan on Jovial Dragon blog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/japan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Japan on Jovial Dragon blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 03:23:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/japan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Closing thoughts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/closing-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 03:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/closing-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The good:
 Japan was actually surprisingly green. In the cities, only the flat land is built on, and the hills are left for forest reserves. When you get outside of the cities, the countryside is mostly hilly forests, with the occasional cute traditional town and rice paddies. The Shinkansen trains were pretty amazing. Far more comfortable, and way less hassle than flying. The rides were really smooth too. At one point in Kyoto the train to Osaka was three minutes late, and we had somebody come out onto the platform to apologise to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A fleeting visit to future land</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/a-fleeting-visit-to-future-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 02:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/a-fleeting-visit-to-future-land/</guid>
      <description>Today we only had a short amount of time to explore because our flight back home was at 8.30pm (and working backwards from there we only had free time until about 3pm). We decided to check out Odaiba, a man-made island that is known for its futuristic style. We had to catch 2 trains to get there, which took about 30mins in total. The view going across to Odaiba from the mainland was quite awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports day</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/sports-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 11:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/sports-day/</guid>
      <description>As some of you may know, Kimmie is a bit of a roller coaster nut. Japan has some pretty crazy roller coasters but we haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to fit any into our schedule. So to appease her, this morning we went over to the Tokyo Dome. Tokyo Dome is Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s main baseball stadium in the middle of Tokyo. Baseball is the most popular sport in Japan, and every city has its own team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All that shimmers in Shinjuku</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/all-that-shimmers-in-shinjuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 15:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/all-that-shimmers-in-shinjuku/</guid>
      <description>Aloha! After eating the complementary breakfast provided at our hotel we headed off to Shinjuku. Shinjuku is full of tall buildings with lots of signs and lights. There were big screen adverts an people trying to sell you things.   So many noises and funky smells. I felt that I my senses were being constantly assaulted. One of the first things we did today was try a coffee from a cafe set up by an Australian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Tokyo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/back-to-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/back-to-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>We made it to the station this morning in good time. We arrived just after one Shinkansen left, so we were first in line for the next one. It was already pretty full when we hopped on, but we managed to get a couple of seats next to one another. After each station more people got on. By the time we reached Tokyo there were quite a few people standing, and they had been for well over an hour!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkeying around</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/monkeying-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 13:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/monkeying-around/</guid>
      <description>Jase has been looking forward to today, because he was excited to see monkeys. Today was monkey mountain day. We caught a local train from Kyoto to Saga-Arashiyama Station. It was a lovely day and many people were taking advantage of it by hiring bikes. The first thing we did was to check out the bamboo grove. It&amp;rsquo;s nice and shady under the tall bambo. We enjoyed a nice stroll surrounded by bamboo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whale shark</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/whale-shark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 13:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/whale-shark/</guid>
      <description>We made good time this morning getting up and hopping on the train. This time we went to Inari station, which is next to the famous Fushimi Inari shrine. Fushimi Inari shrine is a shrine dedicated to wealth, prosperity, and a good harvest. One of the key symbols is the fox, and there were many fox statues around the shrine.  What makes this shrine so famous are the 10,000+ Torii gates which line the path up to the top of Mount Inari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyoto Kaleidascope </title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/kyoto-kaleidascope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/kyoto-kaleidascope/</guid>
      <description>We didn&amp;rsquo;t really have much planned for today. The weather was a bit drizzly, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t great for the outdoor activities we&amp;rsquo;d like to do. Instead Kimmie found the address of a local cat cafe online. After a bit of a hike, we made it to the cafe. One oddity about Japan is that many stores, cafes, restaurants etc are stuck a couple of stories up a nondescript building. To access them you generally need to use a skungy old elevator with carpet on the wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A magical maiko makeover </title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/a-magical-maiko-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 13:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/a-magical-maiko-makeover/</guid>
      <description>Konichiwa! It&amp;rsquo;s me again (Kimmie), because I wanted to describe my maiko experience in more detail than Jase could. So he&amp;rsquo;ll blog the next two days. This morning we braved the public transport to get to my appointment at the maiko makeover place near Gion. I was nervous about being late and not being able to find the place. Luckily we found it with the help of google maps! I was expecting the place to be full of girls wanting to be made up, but at 10am I was one of only two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mall mania</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/mall-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 13:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/mall-mania/</guid>
      <description>Konichiwa! We left Miyajima this morning with stiff leg muscles after yesterday&amp;rsquo;s climb, but not before trying another local coffee place. This one was actually quite good. They even drew cool designs on the froth.  We observed that good coffee is more expensive in Japan compared to back home, at around $5-$6 a coffee. Jase got a photo from the ferry. You can see the Torii in the distance.  We caught a local train and then a Shinkansen to get to Kyoto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Momiji Manjyu on Mount Misen</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/making-momiji-manjyu-on-mount-misen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 12:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/making-momiji-manjyu-on-mount-misen/</guid>
      <description>We started off today with a trip to the local coffee shop. The sun was shining and it was already getting hot, so we opted for the ubiquitous iced coffee. They&amp;rsquo;re far more popular here than back home. Once we were caffeinated up, we hit the trail to start our ascent of Mount Misen. Mount Misen is the tallest peak on Miyajima. At 535m, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty high (For reference, that&amp;rsquo;s about the same height as Kapiti Island&amp;rsquo;s summit).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deer diary</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/deer-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/deer-diary/</guid>
      <description>Konbanwa (good evening)! This morning we tried to do laundry before heading off to our next destination, Miyajima. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best way to start the day. After our clothes came out of the dryer they weren&amp;rsquo;t exactly dry (annoying since we had to pay for these facilities). Unfortunately as well, we had to check out of our hotel. So we ended up packing the damp clothes into a plastic bag (later we paid to use a better drier at our accommodation in Miyajima).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We come in peace</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/we-come-in-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 13:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/we-come-in-peace/</guid>
      <description>Today started with a rush for the train. There were no more reserved seats available on the JR Thunderbird, so we had to wait in line for the first in, first served unreserved seats. Luckily we managed to grab some! After passing through some tunnels we came out on the other side of the island. We sped past Kyoto which was hot and sunny. Hopefully the weather will still be like that when we visit in a week&amp;rsquo;s time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain rain go away</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/rain-rain-go-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 12:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/rain-rain-go-away/</guid>
      <description>Konichiwa! We woke up this morning expecting better weather than yesterday because of the weather forecast predictions. I don&amp;rsquo;t really trust weather forecasts, and I feel justified in my doubting ways after today&amp;rsquo;s weather! It rained on and off all day. Luckily whenever the weather cleared we dried off quickly (we got wet despite the umbrella) due to the warm air. A forewarning: as a result of the weather, today basically became a food and drink sampling day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World famous in Japan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/world-famous-in-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 11:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/world-famous-in-japan/</guid>
      <description>So today started out much like any other day: with convenience store onigiri (filled rice triangles wrapped in seaweed). It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty good cheap, filling breakfast. Kimmie had gyoza. The combini of Japan are much more convenient that the dairies back home. For a start the combini are fairly cheap, but they&amp;rsquo;re also everywhere. At times literally every street block has at least one combini. They have a pretty good range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan&#39;s El Dorado</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/japans-el-dorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 11:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/japans-el-dorado/</guid>
      <description>Konochiwa. 😊 We again slept well, but as I like to sleep on the edge of pillows, I found the tatami pillow (which was firm and wavey) a bit uncomfortable. Jase did not have any worries. This morning we had to check out of our ryokan. Before doing so, we ate our final ryokan breakfast. Once again we had 12 little dishes to devour. I definitely had my favourites, and tried to save the best for last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty fly for a samurai</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/pretty-fly-for-a-samurai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 11:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/pretty-fly-for-a-samurai/</guid>
      <description>The Onsen at this place are awesome. I swear I&amp;rsquo;ve had more baths in the past two days than I&amp;rsquo;ve had in the past two years. So far I&amp;rsquo;ve been having two soaks a day. They&amp;rsquo;re public baths, but they&amp;rsquo;re pretty hygienic. You have to completely shower and clean yourself before getting in. Everybody is naked in the baths, which takes a bit of getting used to. However when we&amp;rsquo;ve been we&amp;rsquo;ve pretty much been the only ones there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching Japan pass us by</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/watching-japan-pass-us-by/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 11:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/watching-japan-pass-us-by/</guid>
      <description>Ohayō gozaimas (good morning)! We got going at 6.30am this morning because we needed to get the train from Ueno to Tokyo in order to then catch our Shinkansen (bullet train). The morning started off a bit stressful because somehow we got a bit lost around Ueno station, and then even more lost when we were at Tokyo station! At Tokyo station we needed to hand in our &amp;ldquo;exchange order&amp;rdquo; to receive and activate our Japan Rail (JR) pass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossings and coffee</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/crossings-and-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 09:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/crossings-and-coffee/</guid>
      <description>So today started out much like yesterday: with onigiri. You can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with $1.50 rice triangles. We took off to Shibuya. It&amp;rsquo;s at the opposite side of the main Yamanote railway loop. So took about half an hour. The ride was still only about $2.50. The trains are pretty reasonable here. We took the typical touristy pictures next to the hachiko statue and at the crossing.  Hachiko was a loyal dog who waited at the station every day for his master, even after the master passed away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electric town</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/electric-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 23:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/electric-town/</guid>
      <description>Konichiwa! I tried to post this last night but everything froze on me. I think I overloaded the blog with pics&amp;hellip; ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ We slept well after our long flight yesterday. However, that didn&amp;rsquo;t mean we slept in! We were keen to get out and explore even though most shops don&amp;rsquo;t open until 10am. Instead of shopping we started the day at a nearby coffee store, grabbed some breakfast at a local Family Mart, and then went for a stroll around Ueno park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 minutes to spare</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/5-minutes-to-spare/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 13:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/5-minutes-to-spare/</guid>
      <description>So the day started early. We checked out of the Ibis at 4am. We never saw the hotel in the daylight.  Our plane was the second one of the day. Conveniently Auckland has KFC at the airport. How convenient? Popcorn chicken for brekky it was. The first flight was pretty uneventful. I was hoping the Gold Coast airport would have another KFC so I could take a bucket on the next plane for lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School reunion!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/school-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 10:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/school-reunion/</guid>
      <description>After work today we got home and did a few last minute things. I was fairly relaxed but Jase was encouraging me to hurry along (strange, usually it&amp;rsquo;s the other way around?). We then went out to grab some food. I was originally thinking Burger Fuel but Jase was worried that would take too long. So we got Tommy Millions pizza slices instead. All this rushing only to get to the airport with quite a lot of time to spare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I count the minutes, I count the hours...</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/japan/i-count-the-minutes-i-count-the-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 10:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/japan/i-count-the-minutes-i-count-the-hours/</guid>
      <description>Hello! For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, this blog post title is inspired by a Ricky Martin song. Yes&amp;hellip;anyway&amp;hellip; Check out our packed bags:  Can you believe how little we are taking? We are sharing that black bag. I sure never thought I&amp;rsquo;d see a day where I would take such a small bag on an overseas trip. That black bag actually has another smaller bag in it. Just in case we want to buy anything&amp;hellip; Also, I added pretty coloured ribbon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>